Finding Aid for Museum of Art (University of Michigan) Publications, 1946-ongoing
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibition Publications
  - 1968-1969
    - Contemporary Prints from the Collection of Mrs. Lydia Winston Malbin, February 16-March 16, 1969 (Box 6)
    - The World of Voltaire, March 30-May 10, 1969 (Box 6)
    - Word and Image: Posters from the Collection of the Museum of Modern Art, May 21-June 29, 1969 (Box 6)
  - 1969-1970
    - The Square in Painting, July 6-August 24, 1969 (Box 6)
    - The Joseph H. Hazen Collection, February 15-March 15, 1970 (Box 6)
  - 1970-1971
    - Painterly Realism July 5-August 16, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Krishnamandala: A Devotional Theme in Indian Art, August 2-September 27, 1970 (Box 6)
    - In Pursuit of Antiquity: Chinese Paintings of the Ming and Ch'ing Dynasties from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. Earl Morse, September 13-October 25, 1970 (Box 6)
    - African and Oceanic Art: The La More Collection, October 2-December 16, 1970 (Box 6)
    - The World of Margaret Bourke-White, October 7-November 15, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Contemporary American Sculpture Selection 2, November 1-December 6, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Collector's Choice: Contemporary Prints from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. C.D. Clark, April 1-June 27, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Jules Olitski: Contemporary Arts Project, April 11-May 9, 1971 (Box 6)
    - 25th Annual Water Color Society Exhibition, May 16-June 13, 1971 (Box 6)
  - 1971-1972
    - Mexican Colonial Painting: The Fenton R. McCreery Collection, June 27-August 22, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Durer's Cities: Nuremberg and Venice, September 19-October 17, 1971 (Box 6)
    - Walter Gropius: Buildings, Plans, Projects, 1906-1969, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Art Faculty Annual IV, January 16-February 16, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Art and the Excited Spirit: America in the Romantic Period, March 19-May 14, 1972 (Box 6)
    - The World Between the Ox and the Swine: Dada Drawings by Hans Richter, May 3-June 11, 1972 (Box 6)
  - 1972-1973
    - Indian Miniatures: The Watson Collection, University of Wisconsin, June 25-August 20, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Graphics 72-Japan, July 9-August 13, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Contemporary Art: The Collection of Dr. and Mrs. Joseph A. Gosman, September 13-October 15, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Andy Warhol, November 5-December 3, 1972 (Box 6)
    - Art Faculty Annual V, January 21-February 25, 1973 (Box 6)
    - The Form of Cities in Perspective 500 B.C.-A.D. 2000 An Exhibition of Drawings by Charles A. Blessing, February 28-March 25, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Arts of New Guinea: Selections from the Papo Collection, March 28-May 6, 1973 (Box 6)
    - American Posters of the Great War, April 15-September 10, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Graphic Art of German Expressionism, May 13-June 17, 1973 (Box 6)
  - 1973-1974
    - 19th Century Songsheets (American Illustrated Sheet Music), October 12-November 18, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Hans Hoffman: 52 Works on Paper, October 15-November 15, 1973 (Box 7)
    - The Poet-Painters: Buson and His Followers, January 9-February 17, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Paintings from Midwestern University Collections: 17th-20th Centuries" (Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) Exhibition), March 17-April 12, 1974 (Box 7)
    - A Director's Choice: 1946-1956 Jean Paul Slusser, May 4-27, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Woodner Collection II: Old Master Drawings, June 2-July 7, 1974 (Box 7)
  - 1974-1975
    - Ann Arbor Architecture, 1800-1918, August 25-September 22, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Color in Art, November 1-30, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Felix Bracquemond and the Etching Process (An Exhibition of Prints & Drawings from the John Taylor Arms Collection, The College of Wooster), November 1-30, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Drawings from the Sonnenschein Collection, December 15, 1974-January 12, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Calligraphy of China and Japan: The Grand Tradition, February 12-April 27, 1975 (Box 7)
    - Art Faculty '75: An Exhibition of Works by the Art Faculty of the University of Michigan, April 16-July 6, 1975 (Box 7)
  - 1975-1976
    - Images of Love and Death in Late Medieval and Renaissance Art, November 21, 1975-January 4, 1976 (Box 7)
    - The Art of Wen Chen-Ming (1470-1559), January 25-February 29, 1976 (Box 7)
    - Karl Struss: Man with a Camera, February 25-March 28, 1976 (Box 7)
    - A Flower for Every Season: Japanese Paintings from the C.D. Carter Collection, March 21-April 25, 1976 (Box 7)
  - 1976-1977
    - Contemporary Reflections 1971-1974, August 29-September 26, 1976 (Box 7)
    - American Abstraction-Creation 1932- 36: Paintings and Studies by Alexander Corazzo and LeRoy Turner, October 4-31, 1976 (Box 7)
    - The Borden Limner and His Contemporaries, November 14, 1976-January 16, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Indian Art from the George P. Bickford Collection, January 9-February 13, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Art School Faculty (Lee, Ramsay, Smith, Zirbes), February 25-March 23, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Pompeii as Source and Inspiration: Reflections in Eighteenth-and Nineteenth-Century Art, April 7-May 15, 1977 (Box 7)
  - 1977-1978
    - Alfred Stevens, September 9-October 16, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Works from the Collection of Dorothy and Herbert Vogel, November 11, 1977-January 1, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Chicago: The City and Its Artists, 1945-1978, March 17-April 23, 1978 (Box 7)
  - 1978-1979
    - Project New Urban Monuments, May 12-September 10, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Atelier 17, June 4-July 30, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Whistler: The Later Years [1879-1903], August 27-October 8, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Ludwig Meidner: An Expressionist Master (Drawings and Prints from the D. Thomas Bergen Collection; Paintings from the Marvin and Janet Fishman Collection), October 20-November 19, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Zenga and Nanga, Paintings by Japanese Monks and Scholars, November 26, 1978-January 8, 1979 (Box 7)
    - The Art of Russia 1800-1850, February 16-March 16, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Close Observation: Selected Oil Sketches by Frederic E. Church, March 17-April 29, 1979 (Box 7)
    - From Delacroix to Cezanne: French Watercolor Landscapes of the Nineteenth Century, April 1-May 14, 1979 (Box 7)
    - John Montresor in America: Eighteenth Century Military Maps, April 20-May 26, 1979 (Box 7)
  - 1979-1980
    - Image and Life: 50,000 Years of Japanese Prehistory, August 26-November 11, 1979 (Box 8)
    - The Inuit Sculpture, September 16-October 14, 1979 (Box 8)
    - The Crisis of Impressionism, 1878-1882, November 2, 1979-January 6, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Eighteenth-Century Prints and Drawings, January 19-March 9, 1980 (Box 8)
    - American Photographs: Gifts from the Collection of Marvin Felheim, March 14-April 20, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Helen Frankenthaler: Works of the Seventies, April 4-May 11, 1980 (Box 8)
    - Inside and Beyond: Photographs by Joanne Leonard, May 30-July 31, 1980 (Box 8)
  - 1980-1981
    - From the Winston-Malbin Collection: Various Media and Formats, November 29, 1980-February 1, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Eleven Contemporary Artists from Prague, January 15, 1981-February 20, 1981 (Box 8)
  - 1981-1982
    - The Meeting of Two Worlds: The Crusades and the Mediterranean Context, May 9-September 27, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Roma Resurgens: Papal Medals from the Age of the Baroque, August 22-October 11, 1981 (Box 8)
    - Works from the Collection of Jean Paul Slusser, October 3-November 1, 1981 (Box 8)
    - School of Art Faculty: A Rackham Grant Exhibition 1982, January 9-February 28, 1982 (Box 8)
  - 1982-1983
    - Leonardo's Return to Vinci, May 8-June 13, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Frank Stella: Prints 1967-1982, September 25-November 21, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Nudes from Michigan Collections, December 10, 1982-February 27, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Jean Paul Slusser, 1886-1981, January 15, February 20, 1983 (Box 8)
    - An Armenian Treasury in Michigan, March 4-April 10, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Forest, Prairie, and Plains: Native American Art from the Chandler/Pohrt Collection, March 18-May 22, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Kyoto Metal: An Exhibition of Contemporary Japanese Art Metalwork, May 14-June 26, 1983 (Box 8)
  - 1983-1984
    - Jean-Louis Forain: Artist, Realist, Humanist, June 11-July 24, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Heart Mountains and Human Ways: Japanese Landscape and Figure Painting, [July-October 1983] (Box 8)
    - Gerome Kamrowski: A Retrospective Exhibition, August 30-October 16, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Klipper/Rosenberg: Space, Exploration, Definition, September 23-October 23, 1983 (Box 8)
    - The Artistic Revival of the Woodcut in France: 1850-1900, November 4, 1983-January 4, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Trends and Traditions in Japanese Art March 23-June 10, 1984 (Box 8)
  - 1984-1985
    - Images of the Performing Arts: Music, Dance, and Theater, July 1-August 15, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Gus Foster Panoramic Photographs, September 14-October 21, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Cyril Lixenberg: Design Projects, October 19-November 18, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Sculpture of Africa: Selections from a Private Collection, November 2-December 23, 1984 (Box 8)
    - In the Grand Manner: British Paintings and Prints from the Detroit Institute of Arts, January 7-May 25, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Earth Magicians: Pottery from The Collections of the University of Michigan, March 29-June 16, 1985 (Box 8)
  - 1985-1986
    - Ten-Chi: Prints by Takeshi Takahara, June 7-July 28, 1985 (Box 8)
    - The Federal Art Project: American Prints from the 1930s in the Collection of the University of Michigan Museum of Art, June 28-August 1985 (Box 8)
  - 1986-1987
    - The Rising of a New Moon: A Century of Tabwa Art, April 18-July 27, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Albert Kahn: Architectural Studies, September 5-October 26, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Latent Images: 10 Midwestern Photographers, November 11-December 6, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Ramsay Stuart: Transitional Planes, January 16-March 1, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Max Ernst: Beyond Surrealism, February 13-March 29, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Modern Master Drawings: Forty Years of Collecting at the University of Michigan Museum of Art, February 24-May 5, 1987 (Box 8)
    - The Modern Figure in Motion, May 1-June 7, 1987 (Box 8)
  - 1987-1988
    - Stories from China's Past: Han Dynasty Pictorial Tomb Reliefs and Archaeological Objects from Sichuan Province, People's Republic of China, September 8-October 25, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Native Americans of the Northwest Territory, September 9-October 11, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Shoowa Textiles, December 18, 1987-February 7, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Dream Keepers: A Celebration of Black Art, February 2-28, 1988 (Box 8)
    - Contemporary Inuit Drawings, February 16-March 20, 1988 (Box 8)
  - 1988-1989
    - Mignonette Yin Cheng, March 4-May 1, 1988 (Box 9)
    - As Good as Gold: A Celebration of Two Decades of Gifts by The Friends of The Museum of Art, September 30-December 18, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Pure Elegance: A Decade of Asian Art Collecting at the UMMA, January 20-March 19, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Castagnacci: Elements of Persistence, January 27-April 4, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Michigan Water Color Society 43rd Annual Exhibition, June 6-August 6, 1989 (Box 9)
    - A New Day Dawning: Early Cape Dorset Prints, June 23-September 3, 1989 (Box 9)
  - 1989-1990
    - Prints by Richard Bosman: 1978-1988, August 15-September 24, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Sun Pictures in Scotland, September 15-October 29, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Kiyochika: Artist of Meiji Japan, January 19-March 11, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Twelve Artists from the German Democratic Republic, February 9-March 25, 1990 (Box 9)
  - 1990-1991
    - Indignity and Anger: Prints by Mexican Artists, April 17-May 13, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Sondra Freckelton: Prints and Watercolors, July 6-September 2, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Centuries of Chinese Clay: Early Ceramics from the Domino's Pizza Collection, September 16-October 21, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Bellows and Diebenkorn: Prints from the Doris Sloan Collection, September 21-November 11, 1990 (Box 9)
    - City and Country in French Prints, 1850-1990, October 19-December 23, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Lorna Simpson, October 19-December 2, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Rudolf L. Baumfeld Collection of Landscape Drawings and Prints, November 9-December 23, 1990 (Box 9)
    - The Female Gaze, February 9-March 24, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Pudlo: Thirty Years of Drawing, March 22-May 19, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Margarete Baum: Recent Paintings, April 6-May 26, 1991 (Box 9)
  - 1991-1992
    - Rembrandt & the Bible: Etchings from the Feddersen Collection at the University of Notre Dame, September 7-October 20, 1991 (Box 9)
    - I See America Dancing: Photographs by Barbara Morgan, September 7-November 3, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Photographs: Baldwin Lee, November 2-December 22, 1991 (Box 9)
    - Jasper Johns: Prints from the Kaufman Collection, November 16, 1991-January 12, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Tan Tee Chie: Recent Paintings, 1988-1991, January 10-March 22, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Picasso and Gris: Loans from the Carey Walker Foundation, January 25, 1992-August 8, 1993 (Box 9)
    - The Pear: French Graphic Arts in the Golden Age of Caricature, February 9-March 22, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Story Quilts by Faith Ringgold, March 21-May 17, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Joanne Leonard,. Not Losing Her Memory: Stories in Photographs, Words and Collage, April 4-June 7, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Sylvia Plimack Mangold: Works on Paper, 1968-1991, April 11-June 7, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Josef Hampl, May 30-August 16, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Beyond the Plane: Relief Paintings by Judith Rothschild, June 27-August 16, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Lithographs by Emil Weddige, July 2-August 23, 1992 (Box 9)
  - 1992-1993
    - Havemeyer Tiffany Collection at the University of Michigan Museum of Art, August 29, 1992-February 21, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Old Master Drawings from the Collection of Joseph F. McCrindle, September 5-October 25, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Janice Gordon: Recent Constructions, September 12-November 22, 1992 (Box 9)
    - Vedute e Dettagli: The Photography of Carlo Naya, September 19-November 29, 1992 (Box 9)
    - The Invincible and Immortal Army: Warriors from Xian, November 17, 1992-January 17, 1993 (Box 9)
    - African Art from the Museum Collection: A Celebration, February 13-August 1, 1993 (Box 9)
    - In Focus: Guercino's Esther, March 7-May 16, 1993 (Box 9)
    - The Edwards Ledger Drawings: Art by Arapaho Warriors, March 20-May 2, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Artists Among Us: Michigan Narrative Quilts, May 29-August 15, 1993 (Box 9)
  - 1993-1994
    - William Scharf: Recent Paintings, August 21-October 3, 1993 (Box 9)
    - From Mother Earth: Pueblo Pottery Along the Rio Grande, September 4-November 28, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Hannah Höch: Collages, October 9-November 28, 1993 (Box 9)
    - The Fair View: Representations of the World's Columbian Exhibition of 1893, October 30-December 31, 1993 (Box 9)
    - Larry Cressman: An Installation, December 10, 1993-March 6, 1994 (Box 9)
    - James Tissot: Prints from the Aldrich Collection, January 15-March 6, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Paintings by Mark Rothko: 1945-1969, March 5-May 8, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Photographs by Howard Bond, March 19-June 12, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Whistler: Prosaic Views, Poetic Vision: Works on Paper from the University of Michigan Museum of Art, March 26-May 22, 1994 (Box 9)
    - From Ansel Adams to Andy Warhol: Portraits and Self-Portraits, June 11-August 14, 1994 (Box 9)
  - 1994-1995
    - The Jade Studio: Masterpieces of Ming and Qing Painting from the Wong Nan-P'ing Collection, September 10-November 20, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Beyond Empire: Artistic Expressions of Byzantium, September 17-October 30, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Isamu Noguchi: Exploration and Collaboration, September 24-November 13, 1994 (Box 10)
    - Staffs of Life: African Rods, Staffs and Scepters from the Coudron Collection, December 3, 1994-February 26, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Joseph Beuys: Drawings, Objects and Prints, January 14-March 5, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Divine Illuminations: Devotional Books of the Middle Ages, February 4-March 26, 1995 (Box 10)
    - From Ansel Adams to Andy Warhol: Portraits and Self-Portraits, March 25-May 21, 1995 (Box 10)
    - In Focus: Kai Ch'i, April 8-June 4, 1995 (Box 10)
  - 1995-1996
    - Adriaen van Ostade: Etchings of Peasant Life in Holland's Golden Age, September 2-October 15, 1995 (Box 10)
    - Painting with Fire: Pewabic Vessels in the Margaret Watson Parker Collection, September 23, 1995-January 7, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Stitched, Layered and Pieced: Michigan Artists and the Quilt, October 14-December 10, 1995 (Box 10)
    - 'Unpainted to the Last': Moby-Dick and American Art, 1930-1990, November 4-December 24, 1995 (Box 10)
    - John Stephenson: After the Fire, A Retrospective, November 4, 1995-January 15, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Modern Japanese Ceramics, February 17-April 14, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Bold Strokes: The Inventiveness of Rembrandt's Late Prints, February 24-April 28, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Folk and Outsider Art: An Ann Arbor Collection, March 29-June 16, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Kukuli Velarde: Homage to My Heart, April 2-May 12, 1996 (Box 10)
    - The Weddige Collection: A Gift to the University, May 10-July 7, 1996 (Box 10)
    - The New American: Carl Demeulenaere, July 6-August 18, 1996 (Box 10)
    - The Architectural Drawing including Beaux-Arts Visions: Architectural Renderings by Herbert W. Johe, July 13-August 25, 1996 and Albert Kahn: An American Architect Abroad, July 13-September 8, 1996 (Box 10)
  - 1996-1997
    - Venice, Traditions Transformed: Works from the Sarah Campbell Blaffer Foundation and the University of Michigan, September 21, 1996-January 12, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Sustenance, Sociability and Ceremony: The Art of Eating in Global Perspective, October 19-November 17, 1996 (Box 10)
    - Images d'Epinal, November 2, 1996-January 5, 1997, 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Michigan Collectors (Works from the collections of graduates and friends of the University), February 8-April 13, 1997 (Box 10)
  - 1997-1998
    - Sepphoris in Galilee: Crosscurrents of Culture, September 7-December 14, 1997 (Box 10)
    - The Body (Un)Veiled: Boundaries of the Figure in Early Modern Europe, September 13-October 26, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Spectator of Life: Works by George Bellows from the Sloan Collection (Doris Sloan Memorial Exhibition), October 4-December 7, 1997 (Box 10)
    - Fifteen Visions: Books by Contemporary Regional Artists, October 22, 1997-January 4, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Lost Russia: Photographs by William Craft Brumfield, November 1, 1997-January 4, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Dust-Shaped Hearts: Photographs of African-American Men by Don Camp, January 10-April 19, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Monet at Vétheuil: The Turning Point, January 25-March 15, 1998 (Box 10)
  - 1998-1999
    - Dreamscapes: The Surrealist Impulse (Doris Sloan Memorial Exhibition), August 22-October 25, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Hopes and Aspirations: Decorative Painting of Korea, September 18-November 14, 1998 (Box 10)
    - Master Drawings from the Worcester Art Museum, November 7, 1998-January 17, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Bill Jacobson: Portraits, Songs, Thoughts 1992-1997, January 30-March 28, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Magdalena Abakanowicz and the Mindless Crowd, February 13-May 2, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Seeing It Through: Faculty Artists from the School of Art and Design, April 10-July 3, 1999 (Box 10)
    - Gina Ferrari: Garden, June 19-July 25, 1999 (Box 10)
  - 1999-2000
    - Touchstone: 200 Years of Artists' Lithographs, July 17-September 12, 1999 (Box 11)
    - When Time Began to Rant and Rage: Figurative Painting from 20th Century Ireland, October 25, 1999-January 2, 2000 (Box 11)
    - The Orchid Pavilion Gathering: Chinese Painting from the University of Michigan Museum of Art January 23-March 26, 2000 (Box 11)
    - Amish Quilts 1880-1940 from the Collection of Faith and Stephen Brown, July 8-September 10, 2000 (Box 11)
  - 2000-2001
    - What I See When I Look At You: Video Art by Chris Doyle, September 7-11, 2000 (Box 11)
    - The Villa of the Mysteries in Pompeii: Ancient Ritual, Modern Muse (UMMA & Kelsey Museum of Archaeology), October 1-November 19, 2000 (Box 11)
    - William Kentridge: Weighing.. .and Wanting, November 18, 2000-January 17, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Casting Shadows: Photographs by Edward West, December 2, 2000-January 28, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Mark Rothko and the Lure of the Figure, 1933-1946, December 16, 2000-February 25, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Scenarios: Recent Work by Lorna Simpson, February 24-May 13, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Paradise Now: Picturing the Genetic Revolution, March 17-May 27, 2001 (Box 11)
  - 2001-2002
    - Albert Kahn: Inspiration for the Modern, June 2-October 21, 2001 (Box 11)
    - In Human Touch: Photographs by Ernestine Ruben, June 10-September 23, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Kemnitz Paints Ann Arbor, July 14-August 5, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Donald Sultan: The Smoke Rings, August 18-November 25, 2001 (Box 11)
    - Japanese Fishermen's Coats from Awaji Island, October 13, 2001- January 6, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Women Who Ruled: Queens, Goddesses, Amazons, 1500-1650, February 17-May 5, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Courtesans, Cross-Dressers and the Girl Next Door: Images of the Feminine in Japanese Popular Prints, March 8-September 1, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Kara Walker: An Abbreviated Emancipation (from The Emancipation Approximation) March 9-May 26, 2002 (Box 11)
  - 2002-2003
    - Picasso: Masterworks from the Collection, June 8-September 15, 2002 (Box 11)
    - New York Observed: The Mythology of the City, July 13-September 22, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Ansel Adams: A Centennial Celebration, July 20-September 22, 2002 (Box 11)
    - Masterworks of Chinese Painting: In Pursuit of Mist and Clouds, October 12, 2002-January 5, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Andy Goldsworthy: Mountain and Coast, Autumn into Winter, February 1-April 13, 2003 (Box 11)
    - Auguste Rodin: The Cantor Collection of the Brooklyn Museum of Art, May 3-August 24, 2003 (Box 11)
  - 2003-2004
    - Four Seasons in Japanese Art, July 3, 2003-January 4, 2004 (Box 11)
    - The Romanovs Collect: European Art from the Hermitage, September 21-November 23, 2003 (Box 11)
- Sub-Unit Publications
  The Sub-Unit Publications series (1 linear feet) contains publications from subordinate offices, departments, programs, and organizations within the Museum of Art. These publications are arranged alphabetically by the creating sub-unit, such as the Docent Program, the Friends' group, and the Museum Studies Program.
  Included in the Sub-Unit Publications series are publications which describe the Connoisseurs Club, a component of the Museum Friends group, committed to social, educational, and volunteer activities beyond Friends activities. Brochures and flyers soliciting donations, and invitations to benefit events for the Museum of Art will be found in this series under the heading "Development." In addition there is an exhibition catalog from the Thirtieth Anniversary Project Committee which features the Daedalus sculpture.
  The Docents Program publications include directories, flyers, information on guided tours, and a single issue of a docent newsletter. There are also two histories. The first, published in 1995, entitled A Docent Journey, documents the twenty-five year history of the Docent Program at UMMA including a roster of the docents who served at the museum. In the Perspectives: University of Michigan Museum of Art Docents on Favorites from the Collection the docent emeriti document why particular works of art are or should be favorites of museum visitors.
  The publications of the Friends of the University of Michigan Museum of Art include brochures, exhibition catalogs from their auction fund raisers, and flyers. The Bentley Library holds volumes 3 and 4 of the Friends of the University of Michigan Museum of Art Newsletter (1971 to 1972). Other newsletters include Friends (1983-1984) and the Friends' Newsletter (1985 to 1989).